https://www.alabamahomeschool.org/wpautoterms/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentLast updated: August 29, 2019Alabama Home School (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the Alabama Home School website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://www.alabamahomeschool.orgInformation Collection And UseWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:NameEmail addressTelephone numberAddressLog DataWe collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.Google AdSense & DoubleClick CookieGoogle, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.Compliance With LawsWe will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.Recent PostsThe Benefits of Furnished Apartments El PasoWhen you travel frequently Furnished Apartments El Paso, two problems that you will always encounter are the travel arrangements and your accommodations
[…]Fundamentals of digital marketingDigital marketing has become one of the most effective ways of brands promoting its products and services. It’s cheaper, and thus companies do not
[…]How to Protect Yourself When Choosing a roofing company Savannah GAThe portion of your house which will get the best exposure roofing company Savannah GA to the ecological extremities is that the roof structure. It needs
[…]How to Use Decorative Concrete in Your HomeDecorative concrete is one of the hottest new trends for concrete floors in the home. This flooring system gives you the option to choose which shade of
[…]New to homeschoolHave you been wondering maybe researching home education? Do you feel it is time to start homeschooling, but you just don’t know where to start or
[…]Rigorous Style of Classical EducationBased on the philosophy of education used in ancient Greece and in Europe during the Middle Ages, this is a rigorous style of education that views
[…]AHA would like to wish everyone a very Happy ThanksgivingWelcome to Alabama Hope Academy and Home school! We cover K-12. We are taking enrollment for school year 2008-2009 Make sure you read this very carefully,
[…]Like & Follow us:
Terms and Conditions - Privacy Policy
